A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Subseries 37.4 FA439C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fourth Administration, 1971-1973; 4; 114 microform reels
  - Mental Hygiene (Reel 60, Reel 61, Reel 62, Reel 63)
    - General (Reel 63)
      - Development Disabilities (Reel 63, Frame 112)
      - Mental Retardation (Reel 63, Frame 119)
      - Resolutions (Reel 63, Frame 145)
      - General (Reel 63, Frame 161)
  - Military & Naval (Reel 63, Reel 64)
    - Installations (Reel 63)
      - Floyd Bennett Field (Reel 63, Frame 203)
      - Griffiss Air Force Base (Reel 63, Frame 214)
      - Others (Reel 63, Frame 222)
    - State (Reel 63, Reel 64)
      - National Guard (Reel 63)
        - Armories (Reel 63)
          - Sumner Avenue Brooklyn (Reel 63, Frame 224)
          - New York City (Reel 63, Frame 236)
          - Others (Reel 63, Frame 240)
          - General
            - 1973 (Reel 63, Frame 246)
            - 1971-1972 (Reel 64, Frame 15)
        - Air National Guard (Reel 64, Frame 19)
        - Helicopters (Reel 64, Frame 22)
        - Technicians (Reel 64, Frame 29)
        - General (Reel 64, Frame 42)
      - Division of Military & Naval Affairs (Reel 64, Frame 90)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 109)
    - Federal (Reel 64)
      - Space Flights (Reel 64, Frame 113)
      - United States Air Force (Reel 64, Frame 117)
      - United States Army (Reel 64)
      - Lieutenant Calley Case (Reel 64, Frame 119)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 138)
      - United States Navy (Reel 64, Frame 142)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 144)
    - Selective Service (Reel 64, Frame 148)
    - General (Reel 64)
      - Resolutions (Reel 64, Frame 177)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 181)
  - Motor Vehicles (Reel 64, Reel 65)
    - Department of (Reel 64, Reel 65)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 64, Frame 182)
      - License Plates (Reel 64, Frame 183)
      - Operator's License (Reel 65, Frame 13)
      - Report of Fatal Accidents (Reel 65, Frame 20)
      - Annual Reports (Reel 65, Frame 36)
      - General (Reel 65, Frame 53)
  - Organizations
    Arrangement
    Loosely alphabetical by title.
    - Call for Action - Boy Scouts of America (1973 January-April) (Reel A 1)
    - Boy Scouts of America (1971-1973 May) - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Reel A 2)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges - Firemen Unions (Reel A 3)
    - Fife Drum & Bugle Corps - American Friends of the Hebrew University (Reel A 4)
    - New Federation of Hellenic-American Societies - Knights of Columbus (Reel A 5)
    - People's Campaign for Knickerbockers - Osteopathic Society (Reel A 6)
    - Our Lady of Czestochowa Church - Broome County Republican Committee (Reel A 7)
    - Erie County Republican Committee - The Third Panel Sheriff's Jury (Reel A 8)
    - Congregation Shearith Israel - Variety Clubs International (Reel A 9)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars - The Zeta Association of Psi Upsilon at Dartmouth College (Reel A 10)
  - Parks & Recreation (Reel A 10, Reel A 11)
    - Office of (Reel A 10)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel A 10, Frame 163)
      - General (Reel A 10, Frame 166)
    - Adirondack Park
      - 1973 April-December (Reel A 10, Frame 174)
      - 1971-1973 March (Reel A 11, Frame 13)
    - Parks (Reel A 11)
      - Awosting Retreat (Reel A 11, Frame 92)
      - Canal Park (Reel A 11, Frame 95)
      - Erie Canal State Park (Reel A 11, Frame 100)
      - Gateway National Park (Reel A 11, Frame 101)
      - Riverbank State Park (Reel A 11, Frame 109)
      - Others (Reel A 11, Frame 112)
      - General (Reel A 11, Frame 155)
    - Sports (Reel A 11)
      - Olympics (Reel A 11)
        - Summer (Reel A 11, Frame 161)
        - General (Reel A 11, Frame 165)
      - Summer (Reel A 11, Frame 168)
      - General (Reel A 11, Frame 179)
    - General (Reel A 11)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 11, Frame 183)
      - General (Reel A 11, Frame 197)
  - Personal Administration (Reel A 11, Reel A 12, Reel A 13)
    - Civil Service (Reel A 11, Reel A 12)
      - Reclassification (Reel A 11, Frame 213)
      - Exams (Reel A 11)
        - Disqualification (Reel A 11, Frame 218)
        - General (Reel A 11, Frame 237)
      - Personnel Services (Reel A 12)
        - Merit Awards (Reel A 12, Frame 17)
        - General (Reel A 12, Frame 41)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 12, Frame 58)
      - Alfred E. Smith Fellowships (Reel A 12, Frame 102)
      - General (Reel A 12, Frame 132)
    - Local Government (Reel A 12)
      - City (Reel A 12)
        - New York City (Reel A 12, Frame 144)
        - General (Reel A 12, Frame 163)
      - General (Reel A 12, Frame 165)
    - State Employees (Reel A 12, Reel A 13)
      - Grievances
        - Appointments (Reel A 12, Frame 175)
        - Reinstatement (Reel A 12, Frame 186)
        - Termination (Reel A 12, Frame 200)
        - General (Reel A 12, Frame 250)
        - Retirement (Reel A 13, Frame 16)
        - Salaries (Reel A 13, Frame 83)
        - Savings Bond (Reel A 13, Frame 89)
        - General (Reel A 13)
          - Parking (Reel A 13, Frame 102)
          - General (Reel A 13, Frame 108)
    - Teachers Retirement (Reel A 13, Frame 129)
    - General (Reel A 13)
      - Intergovernmental Personnel Act (Reel A 13, Frame 145)
      - Negotiations (Reel A 13, Frame 168)
      - Public Employment Relations Board (Reel A 13, Frame 186)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 13, Frame 192)
      - Taylor Law (Reel A 13, Frame 196)
  - Politics (Reel A 13, Reel A 14)
    - 1974 Gubernatorial (Reel A 13, Frame 212)
    - 1970 Gubernatorial (Reel A 13, Frame 215)
    - New York City Mayoralty (Reel A 13, Frame 231)
    - 1976 Presidency (Reel A 14, Frame 15)
    - 1972 Presidency (Reel A 14)
      - Watergate (Reel A 14, Frame 35)
      - General (Reel A 14, Frame 55)
    - General (Reel A 14)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 14, Frame 127)
      - General (Reel A 14, Frame 127)
  - Property (Reel A 14, Reel A 15)
    - Federal (Reel A 14)
      - Surplus (Reel A 14)
        - Brookhaven (Reel A 14, Frame 182)
        - Canandaigua (Reel A 14, Frame 193)
        - General (Reel A 14, Frame 196)
    - State (Reel A 14, Reel A 15)
      - Acquisitions & Purchases (Reel A 14)
        - Highways (Reel A 14, Frame 233)
        - Others (Reel A 14, Frame 236)
      - Surplus (Reel A 14, Reel A 15)
        - Creedmoor (Reel A 14, Frame 244)
        - Creedmoor (Reel A 15, Frame 16)
        - Real Property Utilization Committee (Reel A 15, Frame 27)
        - Union Station at Albany (Reel A 15, Frame 33)
        - Utica State Hospital (Reel A 15, Frame 35)
        - General (Reel A 15, Frame 41)
      - General (Reel A 15)
        - Centre Street (Reel A 15, Frame 50)
        - General (Reel A 15, Frame 53)
        - Resolutions (Reel A 15, Frame 59)
    - General (Reel A 15, Frame 64)
  - Public Safety (Reel A 15, Reel A 16, Reel A 17)
    - State Police (Reel A 15)
      - Troopers (Reel A 15)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel A 15, Frame 76)
        - Appointments (Reel A 15, Frame 86)
        - Complaints (Reel A 15, Frame 87)
        - General (Reel A 15)
      - General (Reel A 15)
        - Reports (Reel A 15, Frame 105)
        - Rules & Regulations (Reel A 15, Frame 114)
        - Substations (Reel A 15)
          - Troop B (Reel A 15, Frame 120)
          - General (Reel A 15, Frame 123)
        - General (Reel A 15, Frame 152)
    - Crime (Reel A 15, Reel A 16)
      - Cargo Thefts & Security (Reel A 15, Frame 214)
      - Control Planning (Reel A 15, Frame 231)
      - Crime Victims Compensation Board (Reel A 16, Frame 14)
      - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Reel A 16, Frame 25)
      - General (Reel A 16)
        - 1973 (Reel A 16, Frame 32)
    - Fire (Reel A 16, Frame 49)
    - Crime (Reel A 16)
      - General (Reel A 16, Frame 53)
        - 1971-1972 (Reel A 16, Frame 105)
    - Firearms (Reel A 16, Frame 105)
    - Highways (Reel A 16, Reel A 17)
      - Drinking Drivers (Reel A 16, Frame 169)
      - Traffic (Reel A 16)
        - Safety Committee (Reel A 16, Frame 172)
        - Seat Belts (Reel A 16, Frame 179)
        - Speed Limits & Speeding (Reel A 16, Frame 183)
        - Traffic Safety Council (Reel A 16, Frame 191)
        - Traffic Signals (Reel A 16, Frame 246)
        - Youth Advisory Committee (Reel A 16, Frame 248)
      - General (Reel A 17, Frame 16)
    - Industrial Safety (Reel A 17, Frame 47)
    - Water Safety (Reel A 17, Frame 90)
    - Resolutions (Reel A 17, Frame 91)
    - General (Reel A 17, Frame 97)
  - Public Utilities (Reel A 17, Reel A 18, Reel A 19, Reel A 22, Reel A 20, Reel 21)
    - Communication (Reel A 17)
      - Cable Television (Reel A 17, Frame 108)
      - Telephone (Reel A 17)
        - Service Report (Reel A 17, Frame 117)
        - General (Reel A 17, Frame 169)
      - General (Reel A 17, Frame 183)
    - Fuel (Reel A 17, Reel A 18)
      - Gas (Reel A 17, Frame 185)
      - Oil (Reel A 17)
        - Imports (Reel A 17, Frame 202)
        - General (Reel A 17, Frame 209)
      - General (Reel A 17, Reel A 18)
        - Drilling (Reel A 17, Frame 220)
        - Superports (Reel A 17, Frame 234)
        - General (Reel A 18, Frame 15)
    - Power (Reel A 18, Reel A 19, Reel A 20)
      - Atomic (Reel A 18)
        - Projects (Reel A 18)
          - Gilboa (Reel A 18, Frame 47)
        - James A. Fitzpatrick (Reel A 18, Frame 117)
        - Indian Point (Reel A 18, Frame 141)
        - Projects (Reel A 18)
          - Others (Reel A 18, Frame 157)
        - General (Reel A 18, Frame 175)
      - Electric (Reel A 18, Reel A 19, Reel A 20)
        - General (Reel A 18, Frame 184)
        - Reports
          - 1973 October-December (Reel A 18, Frame 238)
          - 1971 December-1973 September (Reel A 19, Frame 14)
          - 1971 January-November (Reel A 20, Frame 16)
      - General (Reel A 20, Frame 123)
    - General
      - Interdepartmental Fuel & Energy Committee
        - Reports (Reel A 20, Frame 170)
        - General
          - 1973 (Reel A 20, Frame 237)
          - 1971-1972 (Reel A 21, Frame 13)
      - Power & Fuel Shortages
        - Allocation (Reel A 21, Frame 18)
        - Commemorative Torches (Reel A 21, Frame 30)
        - Daylight Savings (Reel A 21, Frame 30)
        - Report on Fuel Supply (Reel A 21, Frame 40)
        - Gas Rationing (Reel A 21, Frame 41)
        - Response to N.A.R. Mailogram (Reel A 21, Frame 44)
        - Snowmobiles (Reel A 21, Frame 48)
        - Speed Limits (Reel A 21, Frame 50)
        - Sulfur Limitations (Reel A 21, Frame 75)
        - Sunday Store Closings (Reel A 21, Frame 78)
        - General
          - 1973 November 20-December (Reel A 21, Frame 81)
          - 1971-1973 November 19 (Reel A 22, Frame 13)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 22, Frame 155)
      - General (Reel A 22, Frame 164)
  - Resignations & Vacancies (Reel A 22, Reel A 23)
    - State (Reel A 22)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel A 22, Frame 178)
      - County (Reel A 22, Frame 189)
    - Executive Department (Reel A 22, Frame 202)
    - Commerce (Reel A 22, Frame 218)
    - Correction (Reel A 22, Frame 220)
    - Environmental Conservation (Reel A 22)
      - Parks Commission (Reel A 22, Frame 222)
      - General (Reel A 22, Frame 225)
    - Health (Reel A 22, Frame 231)
    - Labor (Reel A 22, Frame 234)
    - Mental Hygiene (Reel A 22)
      - General (Reel A 22, Frame 237)
      - Hospitals (Reel A 22, Frame 241)
      - Schools (Reel A 22, Frame 246)
    - Social Service (Reel A 22, Frame 249)
    - Department of State (Reel A 22, Frame 253)
    - State University (Reel A 23, Frame 30)
    - Tax & Finance (Reel A 23, Frame 35)
    - Other Departments (Reel A 23, Frame 37)
    - Judiciary (Reel A 23)
      - Courts (Reel A 23)
        - County (Reel A 23, Frame 48)
        - Supreme (Reel A 23, Frame 50)
        - Others (Reel A 23, Frame 54)
      - Libraries (Reel A 23, Frame 56)
    - General (Reel A 23, Frame 57)
  - Social Services (Reel A 23, Reel A 24, Reel A 25)
    - Department of (Reel A 23)
      - Board of Social Welfare (Reel A 23, Frame 59)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel A 23, Frame 82)
      - Demonstration Projects (Reel A 23, Frame 88)
      - Indian Affairs (Reel A 23, Frame 127)
      - Recertification (Reel A 23, Frame 139)
      - Residency Requirements (Reel A 23, Frame 146)
      - Shelter Policy (Reel A 23, Frame 151)
      - Task Force (Reel A 23, Frame 160)
      - Office of Welfare Inspector General (Reel A 23, Frame 162)
      - General (Reel A 23, Frame 177)
    - General
      - Adoption (Reel A 23)
        - Adrianne Schoenowitz (Reel A 23, Frame 211)
        - General (Reel A 23, Frame 215)
      - Assistance Cases (Reel A 23)
        - Striker Welfare Benefits (Reel A 23, Frame 234)
        - General (Reel A 23, Frame 240)
      - Child Abuse (Reel A 23, Frame 256)
      - Day Care Centers (Reel A 24, Frame 13)
      - Electronic Data Income Maintenance (Reel A 24, Frame 72)
      - Employable Recipients (Reel A 24, Frame 87)
      - Foster Care (Reel A 24, Frame 121)
      - Allen Jensen (Reel A 24, Frame 124)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 24, Frame 137)
      - Supplemental Security Income (Reel A 24, Frame 155)
      - Task Force on Deserting Fathers (Reel A 24, Frame 161)
      - General
        - 1971 October-1973 December (Reel A 24, Frame 168)
        - 1971 January-September (Reel A 25, Frame 13)
  - Transportation
    - Aviation (Reel A 25)
      - Airports (Reel A 25)
        - Stewart (Reel A 25, Frame 56)
        - Others (Reel A 25, Frame 93)
        - General (Reel A 25, Frame 110)
      - General (Reel A 25, Frame 118)
      - Department of (Reel A 25)
        - Federal Highway Administration Audit Reports (Reel A 25, Frame 129)
      - Airports (Reel A 25)
        - Jetports (Reel A 25, Frame 139)
      - Department of (Reel A 25)
        - General (Reel A 25, Frame 151)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel A 25, Frame 171)
    - Canals & Waterways (Reel A 25)
      - Barge Canal (Erie) (Reel A 25, Frame 173)
      - Hudson River (Reel A 25, Frame 178)
      - St. Lawrence River (Reel A 25, Frame 181)
      - General (Reel A 25, Frame 185)
    - Bus (Reel A 25, Frame 202)
    - Ferry (Reel A 25, Frame 217)
    - Highways (Reel A 25, Reel A 26)
      - Cross County Parkway (Reel A 25, Frame 219)
      - Cross Westchester Arterial (Route 287) (Reel A 25, Frame 222)
      - Delaware-St. Lawrence Expressway (Reel A 25, Frame 226)
      - Genesee Expressway (Reel A 26, Frame 18)
      - Hudson River Expressway (Reel A 26, Frame 32)
      - Little Falls Arterial (Reel A 26, Frame 38)
      - Local Roads (Reel A 26, Frame 43)
      - Nassau Expressway (Reel A 26, Frame 77)
      - North-South Expressway (Route 81) (Reel A 26, Frame 80)
      - Prospect Mt. Vernan's Memorial Highway (Reel A 26, Frame 83)
      - Route (Reel A 26)
        - 9 (Reel A 26, Frame 84)
        - 9A (Reel A 26, Frame 94)
        - 9W (Reel A 26, Frame 98)
        - 12 (Reel A 26, Frame 102)
        - I-90 (Reel A 26, Frame 103)
        - I-684 (Reel A 26, Frame 106)
        - Others (Reel A 26, Frame 115)
      - Southern Tier Expressway (Route 17) (Reel A 26, Frame 153)
      - Susquehanna Expressway (Route 88) (Reel A 26, Frame 163)
      - New York State Thruway (Reel A 26, Frame 167)
      - West Side Highway Arterial (Reel A 26, Frame 186)
      - Others (Reel A 26, Frame 197)
    - Bikeways (Reel A 26, Frame 234)
    - Bridges (Reel A 25, Reel A 26)
      - Great Western Gateway Bridge (Reel A 26, Frame 243)
      - Long Island Rye-Oyster Bay Bridge (Reel A 26)
        - 1972 April-1973 (Reel A 26, Frame 245)
        - 1971-1972 March (Reel A 27, Frame 14)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Bridge (Reel A 27, Frame 36)
      - Pearl Street at Wellsville (Reel A 27, Frame 37)
      - Tappan Zee Bridge (Reel A 27, Frame 44)
      - Others (Reel A 27, Frame 49)
      - General (Reel A 27, Frame 55)
    - General (Reel A 27)
      - Federal Highway Program (Reel A 27, Frame 58)
    - Highways (Reel A 27)
      - General (Reel A 27, Frame 91)
    - Railroads (Reel A 27, Reel A 28)
      - Long Island Railroad (LIRR) (Reel A 27, Frame 149)
      - Penn Central
        - Commutation Reports
          - 1972-1973 (Reel A 27, Frame 174)
          - 1971 (Reel A 28, Frame 13)
      - Harlem Valley (Reel A 28, Frame 32)
      - New Haven (Reel A 28, Frame 44)
      - New York Central (Reel A 28, Frame 47)
      - General (Reel A 28, Frame 57)
      - General (Reel A 28)
        - Amtrak (Reel A 28, Frame 97)
        - Railpax (Reel A 28, Frame 113)
        - General (Reel A 28, Frame 122)
    - Subways (Reel A 28, Frame 188)
    - General
      - Charlotte-Henrietta Transit Facility (Reel A 28, Frame 213)
      - Mass Transit (Reel A 28, Frame 215)
      - Master Plan (Reel A 29, Frame 15)
      - Signs (Reel A 29, Frame 38)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 29, Frame 42)
      - Transportation Bond Issue
        - 1971 November-1973 (Reel A 29, Frame 131)
        - 1971 January-October (Reel A 30, Frame 14)
      - Transportation Planning (Reel A 30, Frame 124)
      - General (Reel A 30, Frame 126)
  - Veterans (Reel A 30, Reel A 31)
    - Division of (Reel A 30)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel A 30, Frame 230)
      - Counseling Services (Reel A 30, Frame 233)
    - Institutions (Reel A 30)
      - A-Z (Reel A 30, Frame 235)
      - General (Reel A 30, Frame 237)
    - Employment of (Reel A 30, Frame 239)
    - General
      - Post Vietnam Coordinating Committee (Reel A 30, Frame 242)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 30, Frame 247)
      - General (Reel A 30, Frame 250)
      - General (Reel A 31, Frame 16)
  - Youth (Reel A 31)
    - Division of (Reel A 31)
      - Young Americans Medal for Bravery (Reel A 31, Frame 34)
      - General (Reel A 31, Frame 35)
    - Institutions (Reel A 31)
      - Adirondack Regional Youth Center (Reel A 31, Frame 40)
      - Amenia (Reel A 31, Frame 44)
      - Industry (Reel A 31, Frame 48)
      - Urban Homes (Reel A 31, Frame 54)
      - Warwick (Reel A 31, Frame 61)
      - Others (Reel A 31, Frame 66)
      - General (Reel A 31, Frame 82)
    - Youth: General
      - Child Abuse (Reel A 31, Frame 97)
      - Employment (Reel A 31, Frame 99)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Reel A 31, Frame 103)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corp (Reel A 31, Frame 126)
      - White House Conference on Youth (Reel A 31, Frame 129)
      - Resolutions (Reel A 31, Frame 133)
      - General (Reel A 31, Frame 136)
  - Miscellaneous and Supplemental material
    - Miscellaneous
      - 248 - 343 (Reel A 31)
      - 343 (Reel A 31B)
      - 343 - 433 (Reel A 32)
      - 433 - 928 (Reel A 33)
      - 928 - 992 (Reel A 34)
      - 506 - 600 (Reel A 35)
      - 600 - 753 (Reel A 36)
      - 753 - 838 (Reel A 37)
      - 843 - 891 (Reel A 38)
      - 949 - 1044 (Reel A 39)
      - 1044 - 1106 (Reel A 40)
      - 1113 - 1178 (Reel A 41)
      - 1182 - 1330 (Reel A 42)
      - 1330 - 1353 (Reel A 43)
      - 1353 - 1401 (Reel A 44)
      - 1401 - 1412 (Reel A 45)
      - 1422 - 1431 (Reel A 46)
    - Supplemental
      - Supplemental files (Reel A 47)
        - Name Files (Reel A 47, Frame 13)
        - Subject Files (Administration - Youth) (Reel A 47, Frame 26)
      - Supplemental files (Random) (Reel A 48)
      - Supplemental files (Random) (Reel A 49)